heddels.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy and Terms of Service - Heddels

### Our Commitment to Your Privacy

Heddels values and respects your privacy, and we are committed to maintaining and using this information responsibly. This privacy policy addresses the use and disclosure of personal information we collect from you. By visiting our website, or providing your information to us, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy.

### Use and Collection of Information

Heddels collects customer information in an effort to improve your experience, to communicate with you about our content and promotions, and to enhance and improve the performance and accuracy of our operations and website. We collect information such as your name, e-mail and postal address and credit card numbers that you provide to us when you place an order, when you save your information with us or when you participate in a sweepstakes or promotion. We may use your information collected online to process and fulfill your order. We also collect e-mail addresses at various locations within the site including when you sign up for our newsletter or enter into a contest or giveaway. In addition, we maintain a record of your comments and whatever else might enable us to enhance and personalize your experience.

In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, Heddels may disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

You can always review, update and remove your information by contacting us at info@heddels.com. When you update your personal information, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

Heddels may store some information on your computer in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. These files allow us to tailor our website to reflect your listed or historical preferences. Most web browsers allow web users to exercise control over such files on their computers by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying the user when such a file is stored. Please refer to your browser’s instructions to learn about those functions. Please note that if you disable or delete these files you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable. These and other technologies also allow delivery of advertising that directly relates to offers that may be of interest to you.

We also use other methods of automatic collection to determine information about visitors to our website, including your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use the information obtained using these tools to provide better customer service, enhance our product offerings, and detect potential misuse or fraud.

### Security

Heddels works to protect the security of your information during order transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts order information you transmit. While we implement these and other security measures on our site, please note that 100% security is not always possible. You play a role in protecting your information as well. Because your password permits access to your personal information, please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others.

### Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [contact us](http://heddels.myshopify.com/pages/contact-us).

### Site Contents

Unless otherwise noted, the design of the Site, the Site as a whole, and all materials that are part of the Site (collectively, ‘Contents’) are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress or other intellectual properties owned, controlled or licensed by Heddels or its subsidiaries. The Contents are intended solely for your personal, noncommercial use. You may copy other Contents displayed on the Site for your personal, noncommercial use only. No right, title or interest in any Contents is granted or transferred to you as a result of any such copying. Except as noted above, you may not reproduce, publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or exploit in any way, any of the Contents or the Site. Unauthorized use of the Contents is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. Heddels reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in its sole discretion.

We welcome your comments and feedback regarding our Site, our products and our services (collectively, “Comments”). Any Comments posted or sent to the website shall be and will remain the exclusive property of Heddels. Submission of any Comments to the Website shall be deemed an assignment to Heddels of all intellectual property rights, titles and interest in and to such Comments. Such Comments will not be treated as confidential information. We shall have all rights to use, reproduce, publish, distribute and otherwise disclose such Comments for any purpose without restriction without providing any compensation to you.

### Links to other Websites and Services

We may provide links to the sites of other companies and certain other businesses. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any of these businesses or individuals or the content of their Websites. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, product, and content of all these and any other third parties. You should carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use.

### Site Policies, Modification, and Severability

We reserve the right to make changes to our Site, policies, and these Terms at any time. If any of these terms shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that term shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining term.

### Term; Termination

These Terms are effective unless and until terminated by Heddels. We may terminate these Terms without notice and at any time. In the event of termination, you are no longer authorized to access the Site and the restrictions imposed on you with respect to the Contents and the disclaimers, indemnities, and limitations of liabilities set forth in these Terms shall survive termination. We shall also have the right without notice and at any time to terminate the Site or any portion thereof, or any products or services offered through the Site, or to terminate any individual’s right to access or use the Site or any portion thereof.

### Notice

We may deliver notice to you by means of electronic mail, a general notice on the site, or by written communication delivered by mail.

### Disclaimer of Liability

Heddels shall not be responsible for and disclaims all liability for any loss, liability, damage (whether direct, indirect or consequential), personal injury or expense of any nature whatsoever which may be suffered by you or any third party (including your company), as a result of or which may be attributable, directly or indirectly, to your access and use of the website, any information contained on the website, your or your company’s personal information or material and information transmitted over our system. In particular, neither we nor any third party or data or content provider shall be liable in any way to you or to any other person, firm or corporation whatsoever for any loss, liability, damage (whether direct or consequential), personal injury or expense of any nature whatsoever arising from any delays, inaccuracies, errors in, or omission of any share price information or the transmission thereof, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon or occasioned thereby or by reason of non-performance or interruption, or termination thereof.

### Applicable Law

These Terms are governed by and to be interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Province of Alberta and in the event of any dispute arising in relation to these Terms and Conditions or any dispute arising in relation to the website whether in contract or tort or otherwise the Alberta courts will have exclusive jurisdiction over such dispute, unless mandatory applicable law requires otherwise. Use of, and copying from, this site is subject to our Terms.
